#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ linhnguyenthu912 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Microsoft Office
Teamwork
English

# Nguyen Thu Linh

Software Quality Assurance Tester Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

### Summary

Currently a software testing specialist at Lotus Quality Assurance.

3+ years of experience in the area of Software Testing (Manual) with good understanding of Test Planning, Test Design, Test Execution, Defect Reporting and Tracking.

Knowledge of Java and JavaScript.

Learning Automation Testing.

Well acquainted with all phases of SDLC and STLC.

Self-motivated, eager to learn and highly ethical in all work related assignments thus able to immediately contribute to corporate goals and objects.

Good written communication, interpersonal skill, proven team player with an analytical mind bent to problem solving and delivering solutions.

## Experience

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

British University Vietnam Software Tester May 2023 - Present (1 year 11 months)

- Testing the systems built by vendors for the use of the business users at BUV.
- Liaising with the departments of the University and the vendors to help deliver systems that meet the needs of the business users.

LQA | Lotus Quality Assurance Software Quality Assurance Tester October 2020 - June 2023 (2 years 9 months) Taking part in different projects with clients from overseas (mostly Japan and America) as a Software Tester. My main tasks were:

- Studying the requirements
- Writing and executing test plans and test cases
- Developing automated test scripts mostly in Javascript using Playwright or Cypress frameworks
- Managing bugs and defects
- Leading a small team

Glammie - Online Clothing Consigment Store Co-Founder April 2018 - August 2020 (2 years 5 months)

- Vietnam
- Co-creating the brand Glammie.vn Vietnam's biggest online clothing consignment store
- Managing sales operations and customer service

Cambridge Education Group Student Recruitment Manager March 2016 - July 2016 (5 months) Hanoi

Agent relationship manager

#### Education

Foreign Trade University

Bachelor's degree, Economics and International Business · (2010 - 2013)

**Ewha Womans University** 

Exchange Student, business · (2012 - 2012)